A Guide to the Publicity Photographs of U. S. Senator Hugh Scott, 1958-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Publicity Photographs of U. S. Senator Hugh Scott 1958-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10200-aj
The collection consists of 495 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Info
The negatives were a gift of the United States Senate Historical Office on May 16, 2008.
Scope and Content
Negatives of publicity photographs taken by Senate photographers. Collection contains studio portraits of Scott and candid pictures of Senate activities, meetings, and press conferences. Of interest are photographs of Scott's portrait by Louis Lupas.
Photographs depict Scott with many Senate colleagues and national figures including Konrad Adenauer, George Aiken, Spiro Agnew, Gordon Allott, J. Glenn Beall, David Ben-Gurion, Hale Boggs, Willy Brandt, Edward Brooke, Prescott S. Bush, Clifford Case, Joe Clark, John S. Cooper, Walter Cronkite, John Danforth, Thomas Dewey, Douglas Dillon, Everett Dirkson, Thomas Dodd, Bob Dole, Peter Dominick, Paul Douglas, Abba Eben, Dwight Eisenhower, Hiram Fong, Gerald Ford, James Fulbright, Arthur Goldberg, Barry Goldwater, Robert P. Griffin, Cliff Hansen, Philip A. Hart, Mark Hatfield, Roman Hruska, Hubert Humphrey, Scoop Jackson, Jacob Javitts, Lyndon B. Johnson, Kenneth Keating, John F. Kennedy, Ted Kennedy, Robert Kerr, Estes Kefauver, Francis Keppel, Coretta Scott King, Richard G. Kleindienst, Mike Mansfield, John McClellan, J. Irwin Miller, William E. Miller, Clarence Mitchell, A. S. Mike Monroney, Joseph Montoya, Thruston B. Morton, Daniel Moynihan, Edward R. Murrow, Pat Nixon, Richard Nixon, Robert Novak, Robert Packwood, Pope Paul VI, Charles Percy, William Proxmire, John Rhodes, Abraham Ribicoff, Happy Rockefeller, Nelson Rockefeller, George Romney, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr., Richard B. Russell, William Saxbe, William Scranton, Richard Schweiker, Alan Shepard, Sargent Shriver, Ralph Tyler Smith, Maurice Stans, Adlai Stevenson III, Robert Strausz-Hupâe, Stuart Symington, John V. Tunney, James E. Van Zandt, John Volpe, Lowell Weicker, Wendell Wilkie, Roy Wilkins, Willard Wirtz, and Leonard Woodcock.
Events depicted include appearances on various television shows; election campaigns and debates; Senate hearings, including Bobby Baker and Appalachian poverty; social functions; Pennsylvania events in Harrisburg, Lyndon Johnson's inaugural parade; signing of the Civil Rights Act, 1964; a filibuster on civil rights.
Contents List
- 1958 July 17 Head shot with note "no glasses - best" (1a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1958 July 17 Head shot with note "no glasses - best" (1b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1958 July 17 Head shot with note "no glasses - best" (1c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1958 July 17 Head shot with note "no glasses - best" (1d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1958 July 17 Head shot with note "no glasses - best" (2a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 February 14 Portrait (2b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 February 14 Portrait (2c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 February 18 Penn Conference group (2d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 March 24 Senators Clark, Aiken, and Scott in a TV studio (3a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 4 Senators Paul H. Douglas (IL), Joseph S. Clark (PA), and Hugh Scott (PA) on a joint TV program (3b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 4 Senators Paul H. Douglas (IL), Joseph S. Clark (PA), and Hugh Scott (PA) on a joint TV program (3c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 4 Senators Paul H. Douglas (IL), Joseph S. Clark (PA), and Hugh Scott (PA) on a joint TV program with Max Esper shooting the scene (3d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 4 Senators Paul H. Douglas (IL), Joseph S. Clark (PA), and Hugh Scott (PA) on a joint TV program with Max Esper shooting the scene (4a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 22 Senators Hugh Scott, Thruston B. Morton, and Joseph S. Clark on a joint TV program (4b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 27 putting mail on Scott's desk (4c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 April 27 putting mail on Scott's desk (4d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 May 7 Senator Thruston B. Morton presenting Scott with a magazine, The Pennsylvania Republican (5a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 June 2 Senators Joseph Clark and Scott in TV studio with Congressional Record (5b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 June 30 Senators Joseph Clark, Stuart Symington, and Scott on a joint TV program (5c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 5 Scott greeting Vice President Nixon returning from Moscow (5d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 11 Senators Joseph Clark, Hubert H. Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (6a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 13 Scott and Vice President Nixon discuss Moscow for a TV program (6b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 13 Scott and Vice President Nixon discuss Moscow for a TV program (6c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 13 Scott and Vice President Nixon discuss Moscow for a TV program (6d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 13 Scott and Vice President Nixon discuss Moscow for a TV program (7a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 August 25 Senators Joseph Clark, Kenneth B. Keating, and Scott on a joint TV program (7b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 September 7 Senators Thruston Morton and Scott at the Republican National Committee (7c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 October 19 portrait of Mrs. Hugh Scott (7d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 December 6 Israel Prime Minister Ben Gurion and Scott in Jerusalem (8a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 February 16 Senators Jackson, Clark, Scott, and Admiral Burke on a joint TV program (8b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 Senators Clark, George M. Johnson, and Scott on a joint TV program (8c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 Senators Clark, George M. Johnson, and Scott on a joint TV program (8d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1959 December 22 Scott with an official in Kenya, Africa (9a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 Scott sitting on elephant model, a display by Republican Women of Montgomery County (9b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (9c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (9d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (9e) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (9f) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 March 29 Senators Clark, J. William Fulbright, and Scott on a joint TV program (10a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 8 Meeting on airport closing in Harrisburg, Penn (10b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 8 Meeting on airport closing in Harrisburg, Penn (10c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (10d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (11a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (11b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (11c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (11d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (12a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senators Clark, Barry Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (12b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 April 11 Senator Clark, Republican Chairman Morton, and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (12c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 July 1 Senators Hiram Fong (HI) and Scott receive a 50 star flag from President Eisenhower at White House. Flag will fly over Independence Hall on July 4 th and later go to Hawaii. (12d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 July 1 Senators Hiram Fong (HI) and Scott receive a 50 star flag from President Eisenhower at White House. Flag will fly over Independence Hall on July 4 th and later go to Hawaii. (13a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1960 July 1 Senators Hiram Fong (HI) and Scott receive a 50 star flag from President Eisenhower at White House. Flag will fly over Independence Hall on July 4 th and later go to Hawaii. (left to right: President Eisenhower; Fong; Scott; Lt. Col. J.S. Cook, Jr., Heraldic Branch Office of the Quartermaster General) (13b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 4 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV program (13c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 4 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV program (13d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 5 Social Function (left to right: Senators Scott, Beall, and Boggs (14a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 5 Social Function (left to right: Mrs. Scott, Pat Nixon) (14b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 5 Social Function (left to right: Pat Nixon, Senator Allott, Mrs. Scott, Senator Scott) (14c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 19 Scott testifying 5302 (14d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 January 19 Scott testifying 5302 (15a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 1 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (15b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 1 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (15c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 1 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (15d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 1 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (16a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 1 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (16b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 14 Senators Scott, Jacob K. Javits, and Clark on a joint TV program (16c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 14 Senators Scott, Jacob K. Javits, and Clark on a joint TV program (16d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 28 Senator Clark; R. Sargent Shriver, the director of the Peace Corps; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (17a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 March 28 Senator Clark; R. Sargent Shriver, the director of the Peace Corps; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (17b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 April 14 Scott greeting Conrad Adenauer (17c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 April 20 Scott presenting a book of campaign speeches to Richard Nixon (17d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 April 28 Two unidentified guests, Senators Scott, and C. Estes Kefauver on a joint TV program (18a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 April 28 Two unidentified guests, Senators Scott, and C. Estes Kefauver on a joint TV program (18b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 June 7 Senator Clark; Representative William E. Miller, the Chairman of the Republican National Committee; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (18c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 June 7 Senator Clark; Representative William E. Miller, the Chairman of the Republican National Committee; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (18d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 July 6 Senator Clark; Edward R. Murrow, the director of the United States Information Agency; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (19a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 July 6 Senator Clark; Edward R. Murrow, the director of the United States Information Agency; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (19b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 August 1 Senator Clark; Abraham A. Ribicoff, the secretary of Health Education Welfare; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (19c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 August 15 Senators Bush, Clark, and Scott on a joint TV program (19d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 August 15 Senators Bush, Clark, and Scott on a joint TV program (20a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 August 29 Senator Clark, Secretary of Treasury Dillon, and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (20b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 August 29 Senator Clark, Secretary of Treasury Dillon, and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (20c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 September 12 Senators Clark, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (20d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 September 12 Senators Clark, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (21a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 September 12 Senators Clark, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (21b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 September 12 Senators Clark, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (21c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 December 20 Roscoe Drummond, of NY Herald-Tribune and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (21d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1961 December 20 Roscoe Drummond, of NY Herald-Tribune and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (22a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 January 9 Press Conference (22b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 March 13 Senators Thomas J. Dodd and Scott on a joint TV program (22c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 May 1 Senators Scott and Prescott Bush on a joint TV program (22d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 July 2 Senators Jackson and Scott on a joint TV program (23a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 July 12 Portrait with glasses (23b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 July 18 Scott with petitions (23c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 July 18 Scott with petitions (23d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 July 31 Sargent Shriver, the director of the Peace Corps and Scott on a joint TV program (24a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 August 16 Congressman James E. Van Zandt and Scott on a joint TV program (24b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 August 16 Congressman James E. Van Zandt and Scott on a joint TV program (24c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 August 16 Congressman James E. Van Zandt and Scott on a joint TV program (24d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 August 29 Senators Robert S. Kerr and Scott on a joint TV program (25a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 September 5 Informal shot of Scott (candid) (25b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 September 5 Informal shot of Scott (candid) (25c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 September 5 Informal shot of Scott (candid) (25d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 September 26 Senators Gordon Allott and Scott on a joint TV program (26a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 September 26 Senators Gordon Allott and Scott on a joint TV program (26b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (26c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (26d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (27a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 October 30 Layout of Pictures from televised election debate: Senators Scott versus Humphrey (27b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1965 January 20 Scott rides with Governor William and Mary Scranton in Lyndon B. Johnson Inaugural Parade (27c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1965 January 20 Scott rides with Governor William and Mary Scranton in Lyndon B. Johnson Inaugural Parade (27d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1967 August 2 Copies of informal (candid) portraits (27e) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 December 11 Press conference (28a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1962 December 11 Press conference (28b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 January 8 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV show (28c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 January 8 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV show (28d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 January 8 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV show (29a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 January 8 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV show (29b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 February 1 Scott and William E. Miller, the Chairman of the Republican National Committee (29c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 February 1 Scott and William E. Miller, the Chairman of the Republican National Committee (29d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 February 2 Informal shot of Scott (candid) on office sofa (30a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 5 Senators Clark, Peter H. Dominick, and Scott on a joint TV program (30b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 5 Senators Clark, Peter H. Dominick, and Scott on a joint TV program (30c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 8 Scott campaign photos (30d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 8 Scott campaign photos (31a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 8 Scott campaign photos (31b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 8 Scott campaign photos (31c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 8 Scott campaign photos (31d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 19 Senator Clark; W. Willard Wirtz, Secretary of Labor; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (32a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 March 19 Senator Clark; W. Willard Wirtz, Secretary of Labor; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (32b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 Senator Clark; John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (32c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 Senator Clark; John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (32d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (33a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (33b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (33c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 2 John K. Tabor, PA Secretary of Commerce and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (33d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 April 30 Assistant Secretary of Commerce Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr. and Senator Scott (34a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (34b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (34c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (34d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (35a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (35b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 9 Goldwater Dinner: Scott with Mr. Pitcain (35c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 13 Senator Clark; Francis Keppel, the Commissioner of Office of Education; and Scott on a joint TV program (35d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 May 13 Senator Clark; Francis Keppel, the Commissioner of Office of Education; and Scott on a joint TV program (36a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 June 7 Senators Clark, Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (36b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 June 7 Senators Clark, Goldwater, and Scott on a joint TV program (36c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 2 Senators Clark, Morton, and Scott on a joint TV program (36d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 2 Senators Clark, Morton, and Scott on a joint TV program (37a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 23 Scott, Senator Morton, and Secretary of Labor Wirtz at Senate commerce railroad hearings (37b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 23 Scott, Senator Morton, and Secretary of Labor Wirtz at Senate commerce railroad hearings (37c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 25 Senate Commerce Committee: Roy Wilkins, NAACP witness (37d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 25 Senate Commerce Committee: Roy Wilkins, NAACP witness (38a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 25 Senate Commerce Committee: Roy Wilkins, NAACP witness (38b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 July 25 Senate Commerce Committee: Roy Wilkins, NAACP witness (38c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 October 1 Senators Clark, Everett Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (38d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 October 1 Senators Clark, Everett Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (39a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 10 Senators Clark, A.S. "Mike" Monroney, and Scott on a joint TV program (39b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 10 Senators Clark, A.S. "Mike" Monroney, and Scott on a joint TV program (39c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (39d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (40a) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (40b) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (40c) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (40d) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 1963 December 12 Scott speaking about a newsreel story on the closing of a Philadelphia Navy Yard (41a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1963 Anne Blair, Triangle Network Correspondent; Senators Clark; Scott; and Mr. Richard Rendell on a joint TV program (41b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1963 Anne Blair, Triangle Network Correspondent; Senators Clark; Scott; and Mr. Richard Rendell on a joint TV program (41c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 January 27 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (41d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 January 27 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (42a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 January 27 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (42b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 January 27 Senators Clark, Humphrey, and Scott on a joint TV program (42c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (42d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (43a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (43b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (43c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (43d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (44a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (44b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (44c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (44d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (45a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (45b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (45c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (45d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (46a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (46b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (46c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (46d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (47a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (47b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (47c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (47d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott, labeled "best for campaign" (48a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 6 Close-up portrait of Scott (48b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 7 Senators Morton and Scott on a joint TV program (48c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 7 Senators Morton and Scott on a joint TV program (48d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 7 Senators Morton and Scott on a joint TV program (49a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 7 Senators Morton and Scott on a joint TV program (49b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (49c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (49d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (50a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (50b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (50c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (50d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (51a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (51b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (51c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 February 19 Close-up portrait of Scott (51d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 11 Scott preparing for filibuster on civil rights by "bedding down" in office (52a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 11 Scott preparing for filibuster on civil rights by "bedding down" in office (52b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (52c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (52d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (53a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (53b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (53c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (53d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (54a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (54b) (Box-folder 1:2)